Your greatest creation is the life you lead
Tarnation is a documentary, drama film directed by Jonathan Caouette.
Filmmaker Jonathan Caouette's documentary on growing up with his schizophrenic mother -- a mixture of snapshots, Super-8,
answering machine messages, video diaries, early short films, and more -- culled from 19 years of his life.
Herself, played by Renee Leblanc.
Himself, played by Adolph Davis.
Himself, played by Jonathan Caouette.
Herself, played by Rosemary Davis.
Himself, played by David Sanin Paz.
Tarnation is a 2003 American documentary film essay by Jonathan Caouette.
The film explores themes of loss of sense of reality,
rape, schizophrenia, psychopath, texas.
The tone is emotional.